quiz = {
    1 : {
        "question" : "How many engines does the X-Wing Fighter have?",
        "answer" : "Four"
    },
    2 : {
        "question" : "C-3P0 is fluent in how many languages?",
        "answer" : "60 million"
    },
    3 : {
        "question" : "Who killed the four Jedi Masters: Saesee Tinn, Mace Windu, Kit Fisto, and Agen Kolar?",
        "answer" : "Darth Sidious"
    },
    4 : {
        "question" : "What is the name of Yoda’s home?",
        "answer" : "Dagobah"
    },
    5 : {
        "question" : "Who built C-3P0?",
        "answer" : "Anakin Skywalker"
    },
    6 : {
        "question" : "What is the name of Boba Fett’s ship?",
        "answer" : "Slave One"
    },
    7 : {
        "question" : "How old is Yoda when he dies?",
        "answer" : "900"
    },
    8 : {
        "question" : "Who is the young Jedi Knight who becomes Darth Vader?",
        "answer" : "Anakin Skywalker"
    },
    9 : {
        "question" : "Who killed Han Solo?",
        "answer" : "Kylo Ren"
    },
    10 : {
        "question" : "Who is the First Order’s supreme leader?",
        "answer" : "Snoke"
    },
    11 : {
        "question" : "Who was the Jedi master that ordered to create clones?",
        "answer" : "Syfo Dyas"
    },
    12 : {
        "question" : "What is the name of Han’s friend running the cloud city of Bespin?",
        "answer" : "Lando Calrissian"
    },
    13 : {
        "question" : "What is the name of Han Solo’s ship?",
        "answer" : "Millenium Falcon"
    },
    14 : {
        "question" : "Which arm did Count Dooku cut off of Anakin?",
        "answer" : "Right Arm"
    },
    15 : {
        "question" : "While the Jedi use a number of crystal colors for their lightsabers, what color is preferred by the Sith?",
        "answer" : "Red"
    },
    16 : {
        "question" : "What is Chewbacca’s weapon of choice?",
        "answer" : "Bowcaster"
    },
    17 : {
        "question" : "What are the creatures, living on Endor, that helped the Rebel’s to defeat the second Death Star?",
        "answer" : "Ewoks"
    },
    18 : {
        "question" : "What race does Jar Jar Binks belong to?",
        "answer" : "Gungan"
    },
    19 : {
        "question" : "What color is the first lightsaber Rey uses?",
        "answer" : "Blue"
    },
    20 : {
        "question" : "What color was Obi Wan Kenobi’s lightsaber when he defeated Darth Maul?",
        "answer" : "Green"
    }
}